hello Linda speaking
hello Linda
this is sue yeah
what's wrong I have a question concerning the flu shot
what exactly is it
are your children getting vaccinated against the flu
this year oh yes
they did go to the hospital last week
how about your child my child is also vaccinated
I and my husband got one too
my husband doesn't get vaccines why
he says he is never ill
this is also okay
but vaccination is one way to prevent disease
I know but my husband doesn't want to
last year both of my children became quite ill
I simply want to make sure they're safe
in case something bad happens
all right I'll plan an appointment for all of us
let's have a picnic next week
the kids will be very happy
great idea see you next week